question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
        "question": "Minecraft can be played with a virtual reality headset.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
    },
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The song &quot;Megalovania&quot; by Toby Fox made its third appearence in the 2015 RPG &quot;"
                 "Undertale&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Luigi is taller than Mario?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Gordon Freeman, the protagonist of &quot;Half-Life&quot;, is said to have once had a ponytail.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "&quot;Undertale&quot; is an RPG created by Toby Fox and released in 2015.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Mario Kart 64&quot;, Waluigi is a playable character.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "In &quot;Sonic Adventure&quot;, you are able to transform into Super Sonic at will after completing the main story.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The shotgun appears in every numbered Resident Evil game.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "The game &quot;Jetpack Joyride&quot; was created by &quot;Redbrick Studios&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "question": "Faust is a playable character in &quot;Guilty Gear Xrd Revelator&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
